export const QUIZ_CONTENT = {
  title: "九九②",
  subject: "blue",
  category: "basic",
  data: [
    {
    id: "01",
    question: "4×5",
    answers: ["18", "19", "20", "21"],
    correct: "20",
    hint: "4が5回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×5=20だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "02",
    question: "4×6",
    answers: ["22", "23", "24", "25"],
    correct: "24",
    hint: "4が6回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×6=24だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "03",
    question: "4×7",
    answers: ["26", "27", "28", "29"],
    correct: "28",
    hint: "4が7回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×7=28だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "04",
    question: "4×8",
    answers: ["30", "31", "32", "33"],
    correct: "32",
    hint: "4が8回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×8=32だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
    {
    id: "05",
    question: "4×9",
    answers: ["34", "35", "36", "37"],
    correct: "36",
    hint: "4が9回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×9=36だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "06",
    question: "4×10",
    answers: ["38", "39", "40", "41"],
    correct: "40",
    hint: "4が10回だよ！",
    explanation: "4×10=40だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "07",
    question: "5×5",
    answers: ["20", "21", "22", "25"],
    correct: "25",
    hint: "5が5回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×5=25だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "08",
    question: "5×6",
    answers: ["28", "29", "30", "31"],
    correct: "30",
    hint: "5が6回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×6=30だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "09",
    question: "5×7",
    answers: ["32", "33", "34", "35"],
    correct: "35",
    hint: "5が7回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×7=35だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "5×8",
    answers: ["38", "39", "40", "41"],
    correct: "40",
    hint: "5が8回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×8=40だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: "5×9",
    answers: ["42", "43", "44", "45"],
    correct: "45",
    hint: "5が9回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×9=45だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: "5×10",
    answers: ["48", "49", "50", "51"],
    correct: "50",
    hint: "5が10回だよ！",
    explanation: "5×10=50だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    question: "6×7",
    answers: ["41", "42", "43", "44"],
    correct: "42",
    hint: "6が7回だよ！",
    explanation: "6×7=42だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    question: "6×8",
    answers: ["46", "47", "48", "49"],
    correct: "48",
    hint: "6が8回だよ！",
    explanation: "6×8=48だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    question: "6×9",
    answers: ["52", "53", "54", "55"],
    correct: "54",
    hint: "6が9回だよ！",
    explanation: "6×9=54だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "16",
    question: "7×8",
    answers: ["56", "57", "58", "59"],
    correct: "56",
    hint: "7が8回だよ！",
    explanation: "7×8=56だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "17",
    question: "7×9",
    answers: ["63", "64", "65", "66"],
    correct: "63",
    hint: "7が9回だよ！",
    explanation: "7×9=63だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "18",
    question: "8×9",
    answers: ["70", "71", "72", "73"],
    correct: "72",
    hint: "8が9回だよ！",
    explanation: "8×9=72だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "19",
    question: "8×10",
    answers: ["78", "79", "80", "81"],
    correct: "80",
    hint: "8が10回だよ！",
    explanation: "8×10=80だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  },
  {
    id: "20",
    question: "9×10",
    answers: ["88", "89", "90", "91"],
    correct: "90",
    hint: "9が10回だよ！",
    explanation: "9×10=90だよ！覚えていこう！",
    image: ""
  }
]
}

export default {
  math04: QUIZ_CONTENT,
};
